It has begun. Filming of MISSINAL CARS.
Monster official Tokyo program GO!
Day 1 of photo book shoot. 1 location. 1 focus. I'll do my best.
The ...
reimbursement, reimbursement
Tasty?
Delicious!
Warm
Come on, moisture.
I want you to do something around here, too.
smoke no no
hey
Hello there.
I'm at the Black Duck King.
2p?
I hope it's free and stable.
or not?
bullying
light
Order
harmony
Thailand
dream
Thank you
Day 1, Day 1
Yes, sir.
Wow.
It's over. Day 1.
Thank you very much.
Wow, not so bad.
Japan is 10 seconds a day faster, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
Good night.
Let's go!
Thank you for watching
Back to the drops. My ears are plugged.
It's leaking out of my earphones.
This sound is the clamor of summer
Every time I look for something I love
I can't see it because of the reflection
But I can just reach it
It's so close by
Leaking from my earphones
This sound is the hustle and bustle of summer
Every time I look for something I like
Pushing up the frontiers of time, pushing up the frontiers of time
Let the round patterned circus begin to illuminate
Thoughts leaping into the sky, bouncing, bouncing, bouncing
Take me with you so that I won't be left behind
A place to swim through the seasons
Thank you for watching.
Something happened
Shadows fading sunlight
What do I say?
Quiet amidst the sound of my breath
I got up on my knees
I sat up and looked at it again
Oh, I see.
I wanted to go out
Always keep it cool.
What do you think? How's the dress?
It's fun.
I'm happy.
We're living together again.
Thank you.
Someone told me this is a dangerous animal trail.
Yeah. It's a dangerous place to be if you're being shot at.
If you keep getting shot, the wolves will eat you.
Hide and rest. It's not worth it.
Now's the time to unleash your instincts, Savannahite go.
Doraemon in great danger.
We're done. Content.
Well, thank you very much for a wonderful second day.
It's been a fun evening.
Okay, we'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Good morning.
I like you, Kimi.
I'm glad.
I wanted to go.
And at one o'clock in the morning, there's no one here.
I'll take it here.
Ijk.
me
hey
Take it easy, take care of yourself.
Come here, come here, come here.
I've already pushed up the fronts in the room. Push up, push up, push up.
Let's hang up the round pattern and let the lats begin
♪ I'm gonna jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up
I'll be left behind, take me with you, Rusch, the season's swimming by
I'll be left behind I'll take you with me through the seasons swimming Rusch
Tell me you're with me
Are you with me?
With you?
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
Here it comes.
It's delicious.
It's delicious.Wow, it's delicious.
Delicious!
12th of Mimi's trip, regional ramp.
A number of bicoastal
Deep in the depths of the largest condominiums.
Here's another one with a drink?
Spread out and cover it up, it looks delicious!
Slope is Apollo
Clouds too
Dragon Island
Shadows fade in the sun
What do I say?
in the quiet sound of my breath
I got up on my knees
I sit back down
Oh, well...
I'd like to go out
I'm always trying to look cool
Pretending to be okay
Even though I'm doing it
I want
me
The dream swin The dream swin
Climb the stairs as fast as you can
In the clouds of the wide sky
The frustration that I've been letting out
Gone, gone, gone
Hotter than usual
It just seems to dive gracefully into the season
Something I'm not supposed to tell you.
What's wrong? I'm in love.
It's over!
Not at all, you might think.
Yay!
It's all over!
It's over!
Yes, it's over!
Thank you very much!
The sun is going down earlier and earlier in Japan.
It's over!